

Lorenzo Del Gaudio

E-mail: laenza98@gmail.com Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lorenzodelga

https://github.com/delgalaenza

Phone: +39 3393319673 Address: Casalmaggiore street

231, Cremona, Italy

Overview

I am a **frontend** developer with about **3 years** of working experience. In March 2022 I earned a **bachelor's degree** in computer science.

I have worked in various sectors such as industrial, banking and machine learning.

I have used several frontend side technologies, currently, I am more focused on Angular 2+ framework,

but I'm committed to learning whatever technology is needed in the development environment.

I'm looking for an agile company, having to be able to learn as many skills as possible and at the same time, take advantage of the know-how acquired in the past, to bring value to the company.

I currently live in Milan (ITA), but I'm willing to relocate in case of need.

Please note that my notice period is 45 days.

Work experience

Datavision SRO, Prague - Cechia

08/2022 — Present

Frontend Engineer

I contributed to the development of a product for the detection, storage and management of images in order to create Machine Learning models. I joined a team of 7 people working in agile methodology and taking care of the frontend tasks. The product is based on a client-server architecture built with the following technologies:

Tech stack:

- Frontend: Angular v13 + Material Design, scss, rxjs, ngrx
- CI/CD: GIT, Docker, Jenkins

Goals:

- 500+ features / bug fixes completed.
- · Product used by European leaders in the sector such as Pirelli / Unipol.

Banco BPM, Milan - Italy

10/2021 - 08/2022

06/2021 - 09/2021

Frontend Engineer

I was included in a 6 people team working in agile methodology.

Main duties:

- development and maintenance of frontend components for applications already present in production;
- development of a web application created from scratch with Angular 2+ framework.

Tech stack:

- Frontend: Angular v10 + ngx-bootstrap, scss, rxjs, ngrx;
- Backend: SQL server, java(spring), REST api.

Humarker srl, Parma - Italy

Mobile Developer (Tirocinio)

I attended the university internship in Humarker working full time on the project of a mobile application developed with Flutter

Lorenzo Del Gaudio

framework intended for use in teaching for children with difficulty in learning. My main jobs have been the development of a Unity videogame in C#, the integration of the Unity platform in the flutter environment and the release of the application. Also, I got to write my university thesis with topic: integration between a Unity videogame and Flutter framework.

Omec SPA, Piacenza - Italy

02/2020 - 01/2021

Software engineer (Stage)

I worked as a software engineer dealing with frontend and backend sides. My main duties were: maintenance and customization of MES systems for industrial plants and transpilling of a web application into a mobile application for a direct interface of the user with the planting machine.

Tech stack:

Frontend: HTML, CSS, JS, asp.net
Backend: Visual Basic, python

Skills

Frontend Development:

- Angular 2+
- HTML5/CSS3
- Javascript
- Typescript
- SCSS
- State management (Redux + NgRx)
- Reactive programming (RxJs)

Software Engineering:

- HTTP
- REST
- SQL
- DevOps
- Agile
- CI/CD
- Git
- Docker

Languages:

- Italian (native)
- English (proficient C1)

Education

Bachelor's degree in computer science

September 2018 — March 2022

University of Parma Scholarship in 2020

Interests

Outside of work, I am a kickboxing athlete and have been a member of the Italian national team for years. I am also a martial arts instructor and have a passion for travel.

Lorenzo Del Gaudio 2